表達呢個過程，多謝誒。呢份質詢已經用咗超過二十三分鐘，今日嘅口頭質詢咧到呢度結束啦。議案根據《藥劑業及毒藥條例》。
就批准《二零一三年藥劑業及毒藥修訂第五號規例》。
及二零一三年毒藥表修訂第五號規例動議嘅議議決議案，咁有意就呢一項議案發言嘅議員咧，請你按下要求發言嘅按鈕。我再請食物及衞生局局長發言以及動議案局長。
先生，我動議將以我名義提出的動議，列於議程表內，通過。
Currently, we regulate the sale and supply of pharmaceutical products through a registration and monitoring system.
set up in accordance with the pharmacy and poison ordinance.
The ordinance maintains several schedules under the pharmacy and poison regulations, and the poison list under the poison list regulations.
pharmaceutical products put under different parts of the poison list and different schedules are subject to different levels of control in regard to the condition of sale and keeping of records.
For protection of public health, some pharmaceutical products can only be sold in pharmacies under the supervision of registered pharmacists and in their presence.
For certain pharmaceutical products, proper records of the particulars of the sale must be kept, including the date of sale, the name and address of the purchaser, the name and quantity of the medicine, and the purpose for which it is required.
The sale of some pharmaceutical products must be authorised by prescription from a registered medical practitioner, dentist or veterinary surgeon.
arising from an application for registration of one pharmaceutical product, the Pharmacy and Poisons Board proposed to add the following substance to Part One of the Poisons List.
and the first and third schedule to the pharmacy and poison regulations, a, geico pronium is source.
pharmaceutical products containing the above substance must then be sold in pharmacies under the supervision of registered pharmacies and in their presence, with support of prescriptions.
For amendment regulations concerning the adding of the above substance to Part One of the Poisons List and Third and First and Third Schedules to the Pharmacy and Poisons Regulations, we propose them to take effect upon Gazette to on the 18 October.
二零一三年， to allow early control and sale of the relevant medicine.
The two amendment regulations are made by Pharmacy and Poison Board, which is a statutory authority established under the ordinance to regulate pharmaceutical products.
The board comprises members engaged in the pharmacy, medical and academic professions. The board considers the proposed amendments necessary in view of the potency, toxicity and potential side effects of the medicines concerned.
With these remarks, Mr. President, I hope members could support the motion. Thank you.
議長，各位提出嘅代議議題係食物及衞生局局長動議嘅議案，予以通過。咁有冇議員要發言？
現在各位提出上述代決議題，付諸表決，贊成嘅請舉手。
反對嘅請舉手。我認為議題獲得在席議員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。議員議案。